OK.
好的。
So let's now go through a real example of a personal email.
现在让我们来看一个个人电子邮件的真实示例。
We could also say a more casual e-mail we could say an informal e-mail between two friends we've got
我们也可以说一封更随意的电子邮件 我们可以说是我们有的两个朋友之间的非正式电子邮件
Kate here and Sarah here and the situation is Kate is going to visit Sarah.
凯特在这里，莎拉在这里，情况是凯特要去拜访莎拉。
OK.
好的。
Kate is going to visit Sarah and now Sarah is going to write an email.
凯特要去拜访莎拉，现在莎拉要写一封电子邮件。
Her purpose is to figure out when actually Kate is going to arrive.
她的目的是弄清楚凯特什么时候真正到达。
Specifically she wants to get this detail.
具体来说，她想得到这个细节。
She wants to know that.
她想知道这一点。
But she also wants to show her excitement.
但她也想表现出她的兴奋。
So remember as we talked about earlier in this lesson the form of the e-mail the style should follow
所以请记住，正如我们在本课前面所讨论的那样，样式应遵循的电子邮件形式
the purpose our purpose is to show excitement and also to figure out this one bit of information.
我们的目的是为了表现出兴奋，也是为了弄清楚这一点信息。
When.
什么时候。
All right.
好的。
Pretty simple.
很简单。
We can then be a little bit more friendly and as I mentioned earlier I use the word flowery which basically
然后我们可以更友好一点，正如我之前提到的，我使用华丽这个词，基本上
means we can be a little bit more relaxed about using words we can maybe use words we wouldn't use in
意味着我们可以更轻松地使用我们可以使用的单词，我们可能会使用我们不会使用的单词
a professional email.
专业的电子邮件。
And we don't have to worry too much about being super super concise.
而且我们不必太担心超级超级简洁。
All right.
好的。
So we have a chunk here.
所以我们这里有一大块。
This is let's call the main body and then the question here.
这是让我们称之为主体，然后是这里的问题。
Remember we should separate out the main question.
请记住，我们应该分离出主要问题。
That's what we're trying to get this information.
这就是我们试图获取这些信息的目的。
So we need to make sure it's not part of this.
所以我们需要确保它不是其中的一部分。
Let's just read through it and see if we can get the feeling for why this is a good way to to write
让我们通读一遍，看看我们是否能理解为什么这是一种很好的写作方式
an email to a friend.
给朋友的电子邮件。
OK.
好的。
Dear Kate by the way we can also take dear out of there if we want to.
亲爱的凯特，顺便说一句，如果我们愿意，我们也可以把亲爱的带出去。
If we wanted to just say hey Kate or hello Kate or hi Kate or just Kate.
如果我们只想说嘿凯特或你好凯特或你好凯特或只是凯特。
I'm really looking forward to your visit next week.
我真的很期待你下周的访问。
We can see a lot of interesting places and I can show you some restaurants to eat local food.
我们可以看到很多有趣的地方，我可以带你去一些餐馆吃当地的食物。
OK maybe they're old friends and they haven't seen each other in a while.
好吧，也许他们是老朋友了，他们已经有一段时间没有见面了。
Who knows.
谁知道。
OK.
好的。
So just an example just an example.
所以只是一个例子只是一个例子。
She's just saying some of the things that they might do when Kate visits.
她只是在说凯特来访时他们可能会做的一些事情。
What's the purpose of that.
这样做的目的是什么。
Why would she say that.
她为什么要这么说。
She's not giving any names.
她没有给出任何名字。
She's not asking any questions.
她没有问任何问题。
It's a waste of time.
这是浪费时间。
Well this is really just to be polite.
好吧，这真的只是为了礼貌。
It's also to show her excitement but also to be polite.
这也是为了表现她的兴奋，也是为了礼貌。
If she just starts the e-mail hi Kate which day do you think you will arrive.
如果她刚刚开始发送电子邮件，嗨，凯特，你认为你会在哪一天到达。
It sounds like I have no other purpose or interest other than knowing exactly when you will be here.
听起来我除了确切地知道你什么时候会在这里之外，没有其他目的或兴趣。
And it feels very business like if we just say Kate which day do you think you will arrive.
如果我们只是说凯特，你认为你会在哪一天到达，这感觉很商务。
So by saying this first we we make it feel more comfortable we can show a bit of emotion.
因此，通过首先说这个，我们让它感觉更舒服，我们可以表现出一点情感。
She feels oh wow my friend Sarah can't wait to see me.
她觉得哇哦，我的朋友莎拉等不及要见我了。
She's very excited and now I can't wait to maybe see some local restaurants or hang out or do interesting
她很兴奋，现在我迫不及待地想看看当地的餐馆或闲逛或做些有趣的事
things in interesting places.
有趣的地方的东西。
So this is good.
所以这很好。
And it's actually important to have something there.
在那里拥有一些东西实际上很重要。
You could ask a few questions instead you could say How are your kids doing.
你可以问几个问题，而不是说你的孩子过得怎么样。
You can.
你可以。
You can use things that you know about your friend.
您可以使用您对朋友的了解。
How are things going with the kids or how's your job in these days.
孩子们的情况如何，或者这些天你的工作如何。
I heard that you got a promotion so you can use information that you know to get information from them
我听说你升职了，所以你可以使用你知道的信息来获取信息嗯他们
but you may just be doing that to be friendly so that you're not saying only exactly what your question
但你可能只是为了友好而这样做，这样你就不会只说出你的问题
is.
是。
Because again if you do that sounds a bit unfriendly sounds a bit cold.
因为如果你这样做听起来有点不友好，听起来有点冷。
And it sounds a bit to business like OK.
这听起来有点像OK。
So something has to be there.
所以必须有一些东西。
I like to use usually some questions some questions.
我通常喜欢用一些问题一些问题。
I heard that you're going to be moving to Seattle in a few months.
我听说你几个月后要搬到西雅图。
Is that true.
真的吗。
If so let me know because I have some friends there who might be able to help you.
如果是这样，请告诉我，因为我在那里有一些朋友可以帮助你。
That would be a very simple thing to put at the beginning of an email and then maybe I have a couple
这将是一个非常简单的东西放在电子邮件的开头，然后也许我有几个
of questions I'd like you to answer.
我希望你回答的问题。
Again this is someone I know someone who I'm friends with maybe I have a long relationship with this
再说一次，这是我认识的人，我是朋友，也许我和这个人有很长的关系
person.
人。
If it's a stranger then I have nothing to ask like this.
如果是陌生人，那我就没什么好问的了。
We could still do an introduction or something but we wouldn't be able to say anything like that then
我们仍然可以做介绍或其他事情，但我们不能说那样的话
we say the purpose which day do you think you will arrive sounds a little bit softer than when will
我们说你认为你会在哪一天到达的目的听起来比什么时候要柔和一些
you arrive.
你到了。
That sounds a little too direct.
这听起来有点太直接了。
It sounds a little too direct.
听起来有点太直接了。
When are you coming to straight.
你什么时候直来直去。
When do you think you will arrive.
你觉得你什么时候能到。
When do you think.
你什么时候想的。
Sounds much more gentle.
听起来柔和了许多。
OK.
好的。
Now she she uses.
现在她用了。
See you at the end of the class will go over some more of these and different ones we can use.
在课程结束时见，我们将讨论更多这些和我们可以使用的不同的。
See you is actually pretty good.
见你其实还不错。
It's very friendly.
它非常友好。
It's very casual.
这很随意。
And then she writes her name at the bottom.
然后她在底部写下她的名字。
So in the personal style there can be many different ways to do it but it is important to have usually
因此，在个人风格中，可以有许多不同的方式来做到这一点，但重要的是通常拥有
something at the beginning of the email to give it its friendly tone.
在电子邮件的开头添加一些内容，使其具有友好的语气。
And we need to be clear that sometimes we can use dear but we don't have to.
而且我们需要清楚的是，有时我们可以使用 Dear 但我们不必这样做。
And also the purpose what we're trying to get from the other person should be separate from the main
而且我们试图从其他人那里得到的目的应该与主要目的分开
body.
身体。
You can remember these things you should be able to write really clear personal emails anytime you need.
你可以记住这些事情，你应该能够在任何需要的时候写出非常清晰的个人电子邮件。